One little apple hanging in the tree,
Two little birds as happy as can be.
Three rolling balls on the shiny floor,
Four little kittens knocking at the door!
Five busy bees buzzing in the hive,
Counting our friends,
one to five! One, two, three, four, five!
Watch our little numbers come alive!
Clap your hands and tap your shoe,
Counting is fun for me and you!
Six yellow ducks swimming in the lake,
Seven sweet candles on a birthday cake!
Eight tiny boats sailing far away,
Nine colorful balloons floating up to play!
Ten shiny stars shining high and bright,
Lighting up the numbers in the night!
One, two, three, four, five! Six, seven, eight, nine, ten, alive!
Clap your hands and tap your shoe,
Counting is fun for me and you!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
We counted to ten! Yay!